# ABHISHEK SINGH SIKRIWAL

# **Technology Analyst**

**4** 8319352218

**♀** Indore

@ sikriwalabhishek7@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhisheksikriwal-47915a121

# **SUMMARY**

Over 4.9 year of experience working in Agile environment as Technology Analyst/Software Developer for clients like American Airlines, NBN telecom and seeking a Python Developer role. Experience in fixing issues by analyzing, designing, coding, unit testing, quality assurance testing and implementation. A team player and a highly motivated individual willing to learn new technologies and methods.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Technology Analyst

#### **Infosys Limited**

苗 07/2022 - Present Indore

Company Description

- Part of the NBN Telecom project as Python developer, and have gained knowledge about Telecom Industry.
- Involved in discovery/analysis/coding/testing of the requirement or the reported issues. Preparation of documents - Analysis/ User Guide / Test case summary of the tasks.
- Delivery of product within timelines and with quality awareness.
- Involved in maintaining track of Weekly Status Report/ Timesheet /Query Log / Defect Prevention sheet for easy tracking of work done in Project.

# Software Developer

#### Hexaware Technologies, Mumbai

**=** 06/2021 - 07/2022 • Chennai/Mumbai

Company Description

- Part of the American Airlines project as Python/Mainframe developer, have knowledge about Airlines Industry and worked under framework such as Django. In the given tenure, performed some of the major enhancements for the airline routes like - Dallas-Fort to Hong Kong, Seattle to Bangalore, Seattle to Delhi. I was also responsible for mentoring 3 individuals in my project.
- Undergone the Full Stack Development Training Program at Hexavarsity in MySQL, Python/ Java, Maven, GIT, Angular and AWS and worked on a project -Canteen Management System in the training period.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Engineering in Electronics and communication Oriental institute of science and technology

**=** 08/2015 - 05/2019

# **SKILLS**

Python	Django	нтм	IL _	CSS
Pandas	selenium	Mysql		Pycharm
Visual studio code		Git	Oops concept	
Tableau				

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**



Microsoft PL-900 and AZ -900 Certified.

Received Iconic award from DXC technologies/American Airlines

**Received appreciation from clients after** completing the enhancements related to Seattle-Bangalore newly added airline route.

# **HOBBIES**

Playing chess, Solving Rubik's cube, and guitar.

Reading books and articles.

# **LANGUAGES**

<b>English</b> Proficient	••••
<b>Hindi</b> Native	•••••

Powered by CV Enhancy